Guide to the Time Inc. records Bio files 3009.RG2
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Jones, Richard N.
- Jordan, Hamilton
- Jordan, Peter
- Jordan, Vernon E.
- Josephy, Alvin M.
- Judson, Bruce D.
- Jurgens, Victor Joseph
- KA
- Kaczynski, Barbara A.
- Kadish, Reuben
- Kahn, Louis I.
- Kahn, Louis T.
- Kaiser, Robert B.
- Kakutani, Michiko
- Kalb, Barry
- Kalem, Theodore
- Kalem, Theodore E. (Ted)
- Kalisher, Simpson
- Kalter, Suzy
- Kammler, Ruth
- Kane, Art
- Kane, Dennis B.
- Kane, Henry B.
- Kane, Joe
- Kane, Joseph
- Kanfer, Stefan
- Kaplan, Peter B.
- Kaplan, Izzy
- Kapner, Stanley
- Kapner, Stanley H.
- Karas, George
- Karger, George
- Karia, Bhupendra
- Karim, Nakram Gadel
- Karnow, Stanley
  Thre folders, one folder has "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Karp, Walter
- Karsh, Yousuf
- Kasebier, Gertrude
- Kastner, Joseph
- Katz, Shelly
- Kaufman, Boris
- Kauffman, Mark
- Kauffman, Scott
- Kay, Hubert
  Three folders, one folder has "H.R. Luce" stamp and one folder is marked [empty]
- KE
- Kearns, David T.
- Keating, Bern
- Keating, Pauly
- Keeler, Robert Temple
- Keen, James N.
- Keene, Mike
- Keep, O.D.
- Kegg, W. Boyd
- Kehaya, Dorothea
- Keith, Larry
- Kellems, Homer Flint
- Kelley, Edmund ("Ned")
- Kelley, Robert W.
- Kelley, Mark
- Kelley, Tom
- Kelly, Harry
- Kelly, James
- Kelly, John Redmond
  Two folders with "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Kelly, Katie
- Kelly, Michael J., Jr.
- Kelly, Stephen E.
- Kelly, WIlliam M.
- Kelly, William M. Jr. (Bill)
- Kennan, George F.
- Kennedy, Douglas S.
- Kennedy, Edward David
- Kennedy, William D.
- Kennerly, David Hume
- Kent, Rockwell
- Keogh, James
- Keppel, Francis
- Keppler, Victor
- Kern, Edward
- Kerner, Sidney
- Kerper, M.M.
- Kerr, Jeanne R.
- Kertesz, Andre
- Kessel, Dmitri
- Kessle, Gun
- Kessel, Dmitri
- Keylor, Arthur W.
- Keynes, John Maynard
- Kiechel, III, Walter
- Kiechel, Walter
- Kiefer, William
- Kihn, Albert C.
- King, Alexander
- King, J. Edward
- King, Martin Luther Papers
- Kinkead, Given
- Kinney, Doris
- Kinney, T. Wylie
- Kirk, Donald
- Kirkham, Dr. Frederic ("Ted")
- Kirkham, Ted
- Kirkland, Douglas
- Kirkland, Richard I. (RIK)
- Kirkland, RIK
- Kirkland, Sally
- Kirkland, Wallace W.
- Kirkpatrick, David
- Kirksey, Allie & Shirley
- Kirschenbaum, Jerry
- Kirschenbaum, Geraldine
- Kirshbaum, Laurence J.
- Kitaoka, Yasuo
- KL
- Klein, Robert J.
- Klein, Robert J. (Bob)
- Klett, Mark
- Klingensmith, Michael
- Klingensmith, Michael J.
- Klinkenberg, Katherine
- Kluetmeier, Heinz
- Klute, Jeannette
- Knauth, Percy
- Knight, Christopher G.
- Knight, Claudine
- Knox, Marion
- Knox, Seymour
- Koch, Jeremy
- Koenigs, Carmela (Hibbens)
- Koepp, Stephen
- Koerner, Henry
- Koffend, John
- Kogevinas, Linos
- Kohan, John
- Kolenberg, Bernard
- Koller, Bob
- Kollmark, Erich
- Koner, Marvin
- Kopkind, Andrew
- Koplovitz, Kay
- Korab, Baltazar
- Korda, Alexander
- Korff, Kurt
- Korling, Torkel
- Korman, Murray
- Korn, Jerry
- Kosel, Natalie
  Two folders, one folder is marked [empty]
- Kossin, Sanford
- Koudelka, Josef
- Kovarsky, Vera
- Kovas, Ronald A.
- Kozloff, Max
- Kraar, Louis
- Krainin, Ewig
- Kramer, Michael
- Kramer, Michael S.
- Krause, George
- Krauthammer, Charles
- Krehm, William
- Krementz, Jill
- Krims, Les(lie)
- Kriss, Ronald
- Kriss, Ron P. (Ronald)
- Kristof, Emory
- Krock, Arthur
- Kroll, Pearl (Brown)
- Kronenberger, Louis
- Kroon, Robert (Bob)
- Krotz, Joanna L.
- Krug, Thomas
- Kruger, Barbara
- Kuenzel, William
- Kunhardt, Philip B., Jr.
- Kunen, James Simon
- Kunhardt, Philip
- Kupper, Jr., William
- Kurtz, Howard G.
- LA
- Labaudt, Luciene
- Labich, Kenneth (Ken)
- Labich, Richard A.
- Labich, Richard (Dick)
- Lacayo, Richard
- Lafayette, Papers
- Laguerre, Andre
- Laird, Stephen
- Lalli, Frank
- Lambert, William
- Lambray, Maureen
- Lamont, Lansing
- Lancaster, J. Maurice
- Lande, Nathaniel
  One folder which is marked [empty]
- Landry, Robert
- Landry, Bob (Robert)
- Lane, Walter
- Lang, Dale
- Lang, Laura
- Lane, Laurence W(illiam) Jr.
- Lang, William J.
- Lang, William
- Lange, Dorothea
- Langer, Susanne
- Langley, J. Alex
- Langone, John
- Laning, Edward
- Lanker, Brian
- Lapham, Lewis H.
- Lapidus, Morris
- Lardner, Ringwilmer Jr.
- Larsen, Lisa
- Larsen, Jonathan
- Larsen, Jon(athan)
- Larsen, Roy E.
  Twenty four folders, three folders contain A/V material.
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 1 7/8 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Case is marked, "July 13 '65; Conversation with Ray Larsen & R.T. Elson; Le manuscript #1; Recordreel at 1 7/8"; transcribed - 11/12/65- C Sugarman"
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Contains 1 track that was recorded on 8/28/56. Track runs 1 hour. Additionally dated 10/29/56.
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Contains 2 tracks that were recorded on 7/29/57. Playing time of 1.5 hours and additionally marked 8/22/57 co. Case is marked "Larsen, R.E. - Reminiscences Tapes 7/29/57".
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Contains 1 track which was recorded on 7/22/57. Playing time is 1 hour. Additionally marked 8/13/57.
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Contains 1 track which was recorded on 7/3/57. Additinally marked 8/9/57 cx.
- Latrigue, Jacques Henri
- Larue, Stephen S.
- La Rue, Stephen S(hepherdson)
- Lateiner, Harold
- Laughlin, Clarence J.
- Laughton, Charles
- Launois, (Jean) John
- Lauterbach, Richard
- Lavoie, Rachel
- Lawrence, John F.
- Lawrence, Leslie A.
- Lawson, Philip N.
- Laybourne, Lawrence E.
- Laval, Pierre
- LE
- Lea, Thomas (Tom)
- Le Campion, Hubert
- Le Corbusier (Charles E. Jeanneret)
- Le Corbusier, Madame (Yvonne Jeanne Victorine Gallis)
- Le Corbusier (Charles E. Jeanneret)
- Le, Minh
- Lea, Thomas
- Lea, Tom
- Leatherbee, Mary
- Leavitt, Scot
- Lebenthal, Jim
- Lee, Alwyn
- Lee, Bud
- Lee, David
- Lee, Essie
- Lee, Gary
- Lee, Russell
- Leedy, R. Timothy
- Leen, Nina
- Leerhsen, Charles
- Lees, David L.
- Lefebvre, Andre
- Le Gray, Gustav
- Lehnus, Dr. Donald
- Lehrman, Hal
- Leibell, Molly
- Leibovitz, Annie
- Leifer, Neil
- Leinster, Colin
- Leirens, Charles
- Lemelin, Roger
- Lemonick, Michael
- Lenahan, E(dward) Patrick
- Leo, John
- Leacock, Richard (Ricky)
- Leatherbee, Mary
- Lenahan, Edward Patrick
- Leo, John
- Leonard, Herman
- Leonard, Jonathan N.
- Leonard, Jonathan N(orton) (Jack)
- Leonard, Jonathan N.
- Leonard, John R.
- Leonian, Phillip
- Lerner, Frank
- Leroy, Catherine
- Leslie-Melville, Jock
- Lesser, Gilbert
- Lesser, Gil(bert)
- Lessing, Erich
- Lessing, Gertraud
- Lessing, Lawrence
- Lester, Ruth
- Letick, Birney A.
- Levin, Eric
- Levin, Gerald
- Levin, Gerald M.
- Levin, Gerald
- Levin, Gerald M. (Jerry)
- Levin, Jeremy (Jerry)
- Levin, Jonathan
- Levin, Marlin
- Levine, David
- Levine, Sherrie
- Leviton, Joyce
- Levitt, Leonard (Len)
- Levitt, Helen
- Levy, Maurice (Moe)
- Lewis, Edward T.
- Lewis, Margery
- Lewis, Robert
- LI
- Liber, Nadine
- Lichfield, (5th) Earl of (Thomas Patrick John Anson)
- Lichtner, Marvin
- Lidz, Franz
- Lieberman, Archie
- Lightman, Ben
- Lightman, Benjamin (Ben)
- Linck, Tony
- Linck, Anthony (Tony)
- Lincoln, Freemen
- Lindbergh, Anne Morrow
- Linden, Eugene
- Lindley, Ralph
- Lindley, Robert (Bob)
- Lindner, Dorothy
- Lindsay, John V.
- Lindsay, John
- Linebarger, Paul
- Linen, Christopher T.
- Linen, James A.
- Linen, James A. IV
- Linen, James A(lexander) (III)
- Linen, James A.
- Linker, Hal
- Linowitz, Sol M.
- Linton, David
- Lionni, Leo
- Liotta, Louis
- Lippman, Walter
- Liss, Steve
- Liszt, Franz (Franz Vonliszt)
- Little, E. Robin
- Littles, Dolores A.
- Litton, Martin
- Litwin, Wallace
- Lloyd-Smith, Parker
- LO
- Lockett, Edward
- Lochner, Philip R.
- Lochner, Philip Jr.
- Lockwood, Lee
- Lodge, Henry Cabot
  Five folders, four folders have "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Loeb, Marshall
- Loengard, John
- Loengard Interviews
- Logan, Don
- Loken, Robert
- Long, Catherine
- Lomeo, Angelo
- Long, David
- Long, Elizabeth Valk
- Long, Huey P.
- Longstreet, Stephen
- Longwell, Daniel
- Loomis, Carol
- Loory, Stuart H.
- Lopez, Andrew
- Lopez, Carlos
- Lopez, Laura
- Lopez, Steve
- Lorant, Stefan
- Lord, Walter
- Loughlin, John J.
- Lourie, Roger H.
- Love, Fred
- Louis, Victor
- Love, George
- Lovelady, Steve
- Lovelace, C.S. (Bud)
- Lovinger, Jay
- Low, Robert
- Lowary, Patricia
- Lowe, Jacques
- Lower, Elmer
- Lower, Elmer W.
- Lozano, Rafael D.
- LU
- Lubar, Robert
- Lucas, Fred
- Luce, Clare Boothe-Publicity
- Luce, Henry W.
- Luce, Henry R.
- Luce, H.R.
- Luce, Henry III
- Luce, Henry III - Christopher
- Luce, Henry III
- Luce, Peter Paul
- Luce, Robert B.
- Luce, Sheldon R.
- Ludtke, Melissa
- Luftman, Michael E.
- Luter, John
- Lynch, Barbara
- Lyon, Danny
- Lythe, Harry V.
- MA
- Maas, Marie Menken
- MacDonald, Dwight
- MacKenzie, Eileen
- Mackland, Ray
- Mac Leish Family
- Mac Leish, Ada
- MacLeish, Archibald
- MacLeish, Kenneth
- MacNeil, Neil
- Macoy, Ramelle C.
- Mac Phail, Marian
- Maddocks, Melvin
- Mader, William
- Madrick, Jeffrey
- Maedler, Richard
- Magazine, Minnie
- Magee, Karen
- Magnet, Myron
- Magnuson, Ed
- Magubane, Peter
- Mahurn, Matt
- Mailer, Norman
- Mandel, Paul
- Maness, David
- Maness, David (Dave)
- Mangan, Sherry
- Main, Jerry (Jeremy)
- Main, Jeremy
- Maisel, Jay
- Malik, Charles
- Malkin, Lawrence
- Mallet, Gina
- Mallin, Jay
- Manchester, William
- Manley, Joan
- Manning, Robert
- Manning, Robert J.
- Manny, Daniel Pratt
- Manthrop, John
- Mapple Thorpe, Robert
- Marcom, John
- Marin, John
- Mark, Mary Ellen
- Markward, Henry W.
- Marmon, William F.
- Marmon, William (Bill)
- Marquand, J.P.
- Marsano, Bill
- Marsh, Reginald
- Marshall, Gladys
- Marshall, Robert
- Martin, Alan R.
- Martin, Ben
- Martin, Arthur Dwight
- Martin, Betsy R.
- Martin, Charles
- Martin, Dorothy McDowell
- Martin, Fletcher
- Martin, John Stuart
- Martin, John S.
  Five folders, one folder has "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Martin, Key
- Martin, Linda Grant
- Martin, Mimi
- Martin, Peter Bird
- Martin, Robert
- Martis, Joseph (Pepi)
- Martyn, Thomas J.C.
- Mason, Janet
- Massar, Ivan
- Masters, Dexter
- Mathisen, C. Tyler
- Mathews, Peter
- Matthews, T.S.
- Matthews, T(homas) S(tanley)
- Mattimore, John Clarke
- Mattison, Harry
- Manldin, Bill
- Maule, Hamilton B. (Tex)
- Mauney, Mike
- Mauney, Michael
- Maurer, Herrymon
- May, Todd
- May, Todd Jr.
- Mayer, Worthington S. (Tony)
- Maynard, Harry E.
- Mayor, Brantz
- Maxwell, Clair
- MC
- McAloney, Holt
- McAniff, Nora P.
- McAvoy, Thomas
- McAvoy, Thomas Dowell (Tom)
- McBee, Susanna
- McCabe, Robert K(arr) (Bob)
- McCall, Cheryl
- McCalmont, Lucretia Anne
- McCallum, Jack
- McCandless, Carolyn
- McCarrick, Edward
- McCarthy, Eugene (Senator)
- McCarthy, Mary
- McCarthy, Joe
- McCarthy, Robert E.
- McCarthy, Sean J.
- McCarthy, Wilson
- McClintock, Shirley Sprague
- McCluskey, James J.
- McCoach, Robert
- McCombe, Leonard
- McCombs, Holland
- McConaughy, James Lukens
- McConaughy, James Lukens Jr.
- McConnell, Margaret
- McCoy, Noel
- McCrary, John Reagan (Tex)
- McCrudden, Michael J.
- McCrum, Marie
- McCue, George
- McCulloch, Frank W.
  Five Folders, one folder has "H.R. Luce" stamp
- McCullough, David
- McCullough, John T.
- McCutchen, Richard
- McDermott, John R.
- McDonald, Dwight
- McDonald, Frank W.
- McDonald, Frank
- McDonald, Frank W.
- McDonald, John
- McDonald, Lany
- McDonald, William J.
- McDonnell, Kenneth
- McDonnell, Phil
- McDowell, Edwin
- McDowell, Jeanne Dorin
- McGeary, Johanna P.
- McGeary, Johanna
- McGrath, Margaret
- McHale, William
- McKeough, Richard
- McKeough, Richard B. (Dick)
- McKoan, Thomas F.
- McLatchie, John
- McLaughlin, Paul
- McLaughlin, Robert
- McManus, Jason
- McNally, Joe
- McNaughton, Frank
- McNeil, Florence
- McPhee, John
- McQuade, Walter
- McQuade, Derosset Morrissey
- McQuiston, Joann W.
- McSweeney, Jack
- McSweeney, Jack (John)
- McWhirter, William
- McWhirter, Bill (William)
- ME
- Mead, Margaret
- Meadows, Efward
- Meany, George
- Mechau, Frank
- Mecklin, John
- Medina, Harold
- Medina, Harold R. Jr.
- Medina, Sara C(ollins)
- Meek, Samuel
  Separated Materials Note
- Meek, Samuel W.
- Mehta, Naushad
- Meier, Richard A.
- Meigher, Christopher
- Meigher, S. Christopher III
- Meister, Knud
- Mellor, Bill
- Melvoin, Jeff
- Mercer, James L.
- Merlis, Bob
- Merrick, Frank
- Merrick, Frank (B.)
- Merrill, David
- Merritt, Vernon
- Merritt, Vernon III
- Merton, Nancy
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 1 7/8 ips; 5 in. reel, 1/4 in. tape. Case Labeled "March 23 '65, Interview with Harry Merton, Childhood friend of Briton Hadden, SIB Conversation is incompleted, omitted"
- Meryman, Richard
- Meryman, Richard S.
- Messinger, Curtis C.
- Metzner, Sheila
- Meyer, Herbert
- Meyer, Jan H.H.
- Meyerowitz, Joel
- Meyers, Burt
- Meyers, John
- Meyers, John A.
- Michaels, Margyerite (Margie)
- Michaels, Leonard
- Michaud, Roland
- Michener, James A.
- Michie, Allan A.
- Mickelson, Sig
- Mies Van Der Rohe, Ludwig
- Mieth, Hansel
- Miklaszewski, James Allen (Jim)
- Mili, Gjon
- Miller, Barse
- Miller, Mrs. Chuck
- Miller, D'Arcy
- Miller, A. Edward
- Miller, Francis
- Miller, Frank
- Miller, Jonathan
- Miller, Loye W.
- Miller, Merle
- Miller, Merle H.
- Miller, Peter
- Miller, Robert L.
- Miller, Wayne
- Miller, William E.
- Miller, William E. (Bill)
- Miller, William
- Miller, William J. (Bill)
- Millington, John A.
- Millis, Walter
- Mills, Hillis
- Mills, James
- Milotte, Alfred G.
- Mims, Roddey E.
- Minszenty, Cardinal
- Mintener, Bradshaw
- Mitchell, Bruce
- Mitchell, Emily
- Mitchell, Len
- Mitchell, Raymond
- Mittarakis, Lia
- MO
- Moffett, Hugh
- Mohr, Charles
- Mohs, Mayo
- Molloy, Mary
- Molotov, Vyacheslav
- Monard, Jacques
  One folder which includes A/V material
  4 audio discs (Soundscriber discs); 6 in.; discs are respectively marked "#1", "#2", "#3", "#4"
- Mondadori, Arnoldo
- Monroe, Sylvester
- Montville, Eleanor
- Moody, John
- Moonves, Leslie
- Moore, Alicia
- Moore, Alicia Hill
- Moore, Ann S.
- Moore, Elisabeth (Luce)
- Moore, Charles
- Moore, Elisabeth (Luce)
- Moore, Gerald
- Moore, Gilbert
- Moore, Maurice T.
- Moore, Oliver
- Moore, Maurice T(homoson) (Tex)
- Moore, Robert J.
- Moore, Robert
- Moore, Sally
- Moore, Tom
- Morfogen, Zack
- Morfogen, Zachary
- Morgado, Robert
- Morgan, Barbara
- Morgan, Richard T.
- Morgan, Thmas B (Tom)
- Morgan, Willard
- Morgenstern, Oskar
- Morgenthal, Robert M.
- Moritz, Michael
- Morris, Christopher
- Morris, Desmond
- Morris, Doug
- Morris, Fred(erick) B.
- Morris, James
- Morris, John
- Morris, Keith
- Morris, Wright
- Morrison, Ann
- Morrison, Ann M.
- Morrison, Donald
- Morrison, Don(ald) M.
- Morrissy, John F.
- Morrow, Lance
- Moser, Don
- Morse, Ralph
- Mortensen, William
- Morvan, Yan
- Moses, Robert
- Moscow, Henry
- Moser, Don
- Moss, Samuel J.
- Motley, Isolde
- Mrkonic, Barbara
- Muldaur, Charles E.A.
- Mullen, Jim
- Mullen, Robert R.
- Muller, Henry
- Mulliken, John
- Mulvoy, Mark
- Munro, J. Richard
- Munro, J(ohn) Richard
- Munro, Ross H.
- Munro, Joe
- Murray, D.C.
- Murray, James A.
- Murphy, Arthur R.
- Murphy, Arthur
- Murphy, Arthur R.
- Murphy, Arthur
- Murphy, Austin
- Murphy, Charles, J.V.
- Murphy, Eileen
- Murphy, Charles, J.V.
- Murphy, Charles J(ohn)
- Murphy, James (Jamie)
- Murphy, Marvin
- Muskie, Edmund S.
- Muson, Howard
- Mydans, Carl
- Mydans, Carl Mayer
- Mydans, Carl
- Mydans, Carl Weisie
- Mydans, Carl Mayer
- Mydans, Carl
- Mydans, Carl & Shelley
- Mydans, Carl & Shelley (Smith)
  Three folders, one folder contains a/v material.
  1 computer disc (floppy disk): 3 1/2 in. Marked "Carl Mydans bro disk MAC - clarrs works"
- Mydans, Shelley
- Mydans, Shelley (Smith)
- Myers, Howard (Box Bio93-Bio94)
  Two folders with "H.R. Luce" stamp.
- Myhren, Trygve E. (Box Bio94)
- N
- Nachtwey, James (Box Bio94)
- Nadar, Paul (Box Bio94)
- Nadasy, Ursula (Box Bio94)
- Namuth, Hans (Box Bio94)
- Nasar, Sylvia (Box Bio94)
- Nash, J. Madeleine (Box Bio94)
- Nathan, Wynn (Box Bio94)
- Natori, Youno Suile (Box Bio94)
- Naughton, Eilieen (Box Bio94)
- Nazem, Susie Gharib (Box Bio94)
- Neale, Richard L. (Box Bio94)
  One folder with "H.R. Luce" stamp.
- Neary, John (Box Bio94)
- Needham, John S. (Box Bio94)
- Neff, Craig A.
- Neff, Donald
- Negley, Lowell M.
- Nelan, Bruce
- Nelson, George
- Nelson, Harry
- Nelson, Jim
- Nelson, Martha
- Neuhaus, Cable
- Neves, Irene
- Neville, Robert
- Nevin, David
- Newcombe, Jack
- Newman, Arnold
- Newman, Marvin
- Newman, Nancy
- Newport, John Paul
- Newton, Helmut
- Nicholas, Gouverneur
- Nichols, Mrs. Ruth
- Nicholas, N.J.
- Nicholas, Nicholas J. Jr. (Box Bio95)
- Nichols, Mark
- Nickel, Herman
- Niles, Nicholas H.
- Nilsson, Lennart
- Nocella, Samuel
- Nollen, Emeline
- Norcross, Carl
- Norris, Frank C.
- Norris, Gloria
- North, Anna
- Northup, Stephen D.
- Norton-Taylor, Duncan
- Norwood, John
- Novak, Ralph
- Nulty, Peter
- O
- O'Brien, Michael
- Oberhardt, William
  "H.R. Luce" stamp.
- O'Brien, Tony
- Ochs, Malcolm B.
- O'Faolain, Sean
  "H.R. Luce" Stamp.
- Ogden, Christoper
- Ogle, Edmon
  One folder has "H.R. Luce" stamp.
- O'Hara-Forster, Brigid
- O'Hara, John
- Okamoto, Yoichi Robert (Box Bio95-Bio96)
- Okamura, Akihiko
- O'Keeffe, Michael
- Oldendorff, Irene
- O'Leary, Brian
- Olsen, Jack
- Olson, Jerald W.
- Olson, John
- Olson, Sidney
- O'Neil, Doris
- O'Neil, Martin
- O'Neil, Paul
- O'Neil, Terry
- Opel, John R.
- Oppenheimer, Robert
- Orchard, Thomas
- O'Reilly, Brian
- O'Reilly, John F.
- Ornitz, Don
- O'Rourke, Regina
- Orshefsky, Milton
- Orth, Herbert
- Osborne, Garry E.
- Osborne, John
- Osheyack, Daniel
- Okrent, Daniel
- Ostlere, Hilary
- Ostendorf, Lloyd
- O'Shea, Richard
- Ostheimer, Richard
- Ostin, MO
- Ostling, Richard
- O'Sullivan, Timothy
- Ott, Tom
- Ottum, Robert
- Oulahan, Richard (Box Bio96-Bio97)
- Over, William H.
- Overbye, Dennis
- Owen, A.Y.
- Owen, Deborah
- Owens, Bill
- Owens, Lillian
- PA
- Pace, Frank
- Page, Tim
- Page, Virginia
- Pages, Jean
- Paine, Ralph Delahaye
- Painton, Fred
- Painton, Patricia
- Paisner, Bruce
- Palmer, Jay
- Palmer, William E.
- Papanek, John (Box Bio97-Bio98)
- Pare, Terence
- Parker, Ann
- Parker, Maynard
- Parker, Robert
- Parker, Sanford
- Parks, Gordon
- Parretti, Giancarlo
- Parsons, Richard D.
- Parton, James
- Pates, Charles
- Patrick, Dennis
- Pauling, Linus
- Payne, Philip W.
- Payson, Martin D.
- Paxton, Worthen
- PE
  Two folders have "H.R. Luce" stamp.
- Pearlstine, Norman
- Pearson, Drew
- Peckham, Content Rathbone (Box Bio98-Bio99)
- Pedrazzini, Jean Pierre
- Pegler, Westbrook
- Pei, Ieoh Ming
- Pelham, Lynwood V.
- Pekkanen, John
- Penberthy, Jefferson
- Penn, Irving
- Pepe, Michael
- Perine, Ford
- Perkins, Donald S.
- Perle, Gabe
- Perlin, Barnard
- Peskin, Hy
- Perry, Nancy
- Peters, Grace
- Peters, William
- Peters, William
- Peterson, Robert E.
- Peterson, Rudolph A. (Box Bio99-Bio100)
- Peterzell, Jay
- Petoniak, Steven
- Petre, Peter
- Peyton, Green
- Pfeffer, Barbara
- Phillips, Charles F.
- Phillips, Harry H.
- Phillips, John
- Phillips, B.J.
- Phillips, H.H.S.
- Phinizy, Coles H.
- Phyfe, Hal
- Picker, Fred
- Pierce, Bill
- Pierce, Deborah
- Pierce-Roberts, Tony
- Pittman, Robert W.
- Piel, Gerard
- Piening, Peter
- Pierce, Ken
- Pike, Bishop James
- Phillips, Michael
- Pines, Burton
- Pinney, Roy
- Pitt, James E.
- Pittman, Robert W.
- Plachy, Sylvia
- Platt, Rutherford
- Platzer, Robin
- Pleissner, Ogden
- Plimpton, Freddy
- Plimpton, George
- Plowden, David
- Podhoretz, John
- Politz, Alfred
- Polk, P.
- Pollard, Richard
- Pomerantz, Arthur
- Pool, Elizabeth
- Poor, Henry Varnum
- Pope, Vernon
- Porterfield, Christopher
- Posthorn, Stanley
- Post, Charles Johnson
- Potter, Bridget
- Poust, Fred
- Powell, Bonny
- PR
- Prager, Karston
- Pratt, Charles
- Pratt, Francis de Witt
- Pratt, Jane
- Precourt, Harry A.
- Prendergast, Curtis W.
- Prentice, Perry I
- Prentice, Pierrepoint Isham
- Preston, Hartwell L.
- Prewitt, Ken
- Prial, Frank J.
- Pribichevich, Stoyan
- Price, Boyce
- Price, Larry
- Price, Lee Bell
- Prideaux, Tom
- Prince
- Pritchett, V.S.
- Prouty, Dwight
- Pullen, C. Weston
- Pulliam, Frank S.
- Puner, Helen Walker
- Pusey, Nathan
- Purtell, Joseph
- Quinlan, Joe
- Q
- Quinn-Judge, Paul
- Quint, Bernard
- RA
- Rabbia, Angela
- Rademaekers, William
- Raffety, Sue
- Ragsdale, Eleanor W.
- Ragsdale, Willmont
- Raines, Lee
- Raley, Deane
- Ramp, Irene
- Ramrakha, Priya
- Randal, Jonathan
- Rangaswami, Achal
- Range, Peter Ross
- Rank, J. Arthur
- Rapoport, Carla
- Rappleye, Willard C. Jr.
- Rappleye, William
- Ratkai, George
- Rauch, Peter
- Rauch, Rudolph
- Ray, Bill
- Ray, Man
- Rayfield, Stanley
- Reader, John
- Reddicliffe, Steven
- Redman, Christopher
- Redpath, Frederick L.
- Reed, Douglas
- Reed, J.D.
- Reed, Susan K.
- Rees, Edwin
- Rehak, Peter
- Reichert, Gene
- Reichley, James
- Reilly, Rick
- Reindel, Edna
- Reingold, Edwin M.
- Reiss, John
- Rentmeester, Co.
- Ress, Paul
- Reuben, William A.
  A/V: "Record of interview with Jack Ruben re: [?]- 20 April 1969".
- Rhett, Edward
- Rhodes, Kent
- Rhodes, William
- Rhone, Sylvia
- Riboud, Marc
- Riccardi, Mirella
- Rice, Grantland
- Rich, David
- Rich, Frank H.
- Rich, Marjorie
- Rich, Williston C.
- Richards, Eugene
- Richardson, David
- Richey, Harry & Baker, Alfred
- Richman, Alan
- Richman, Lou
- Richmond, Howard K.
- Rickerby, Art
- Ridgway, Gen. Matthew B.
- Riding, James
- Riesman, David
- Rifkin, Monroe M.
- Riger, Robert
- Riley, Michael
- Ripp, Joseph A.
- Ritter, Norman R.
- Ritz, Gordon H.
- Rixey, Lillian
- RO
- Robeck, Peter M.
- Robert, Elizabeth (Andrews, Denison)
- Robertson, Wyndham
- Robins, Eric
- Robinson, Rita
- Rockefeller, John D. III
- Robinson, Rita Thomas
- Rodchenko, Alexander
- Rodger, George
- Rogers, Arthur C.
- Rogin, Gilbert
- Rohrer, Walter
- Roizman, Morrie
- Romney, George W.
- Roosenberg, Henriette
- Root, Wells
- ROP
- Roper, Elmo
- Rose, Jerry A.
- Rose, Sanford
- Rosen, Clare Mead
- Rosenbaum, Sukey
- Rosenberg, Liz Beth
- Rosenberg, Mark
- Rosenblatt, Roger
- Rosenhouse, Harvey (Box Bio104-Bio105)
- Rosenhouse, Robert W.
- Rosenthal, Felix
- Rosenthal, Jack (Jacob)
- Rospogliosi, William
- Ross, Harold W.
- Ross, Norman
- Ross, Steven J.
- Rosenfeld, Albert
- Rostow, Walter W.
- Rotkin, Charles
- Rougier, Michael
- Rowan, Roy
- Rowe, Guy
- Rubin, Albert L
- Ruderman, Gary S
- Rudolph, Elizabeth
- Rukeyser, William S.
- Runde, Robert
- Ruohomaa, Kosti
- Russell, Chistine
- Russell, George
- Russell, Ted
- Ryan, Michael (Mike)
- Ryan, Pat
- Ryan, Patricia
- RU
  Has a "H.R. Luce" stamp.
- Rubens, Charles (Carky)
- Rubicam, Harry C.
- Rubinger, David D.
- Ruckman, R. Mackereth
- Rudeen, Ken
- Rudolph, Elizabeth
- Rukeyser, Muriel
- Russell, Bertrand
- Rusk, Dean
- Ryan, Thomas E.
- Ryus, David
- Rychetnik, Joe
- SA
- Saar, John
- Saarinen, Eero
- Sabine, Gordon
- Sachs, Susan
- Sackett, Russell
- Saddler, Jeanne
- Sadler, George
- Sadovy, John
- Safian, Robert
- Safran, Bernard
- Safranski, Kurt S.
- Sagan, Paul
- Sahner, Marilyn
- Saint, Irene
- Sales, Victoria
- Salgado, Sebastiao Jr.
- Salisbury, Robert
- Salmi-Solow, Sylvia
- Salomon, Erich
- Saltonstall, Richard Jr.
- Sample, Paul
- Stamstag, Nicholas
- Sancton, Thomas
- Sandercock, Vincent
- Sancton, Thomas A (Jr)
- Sanders, Andra A
- Sanders, Pamela
- Sanders, Walter
- Sandler, Roger
- Sando, Arthur
- Sandow, Greg
- Santos, Gil
- Saralegui, Alvaro
- Sargent, Margaret (Peggy)
- Sargeant, Winthrop
- Sarnoff, Blair
- Sarnoff, William
- Saroyan, William
- Sarsini, Enrico
- Satterwhite, Betty
- Saul, Fanny
- Saunders, Dero
- Sawyer, Bruce
- Sayre, Carol
- Saporiti, Piero
- Saporiti, Peiero
- Saporito, William
- Scallon, Eileen
- Schaal, Eric
- Schanche, Donald
- Schapiro, Steve
- Schardt, Arlie
- Schatz, Arthur
- Schecter, Jerry (Jerrold L.)
- Schecter, Mrs. Jerrold (Leona P.)
- Scheffer, Steve
- Schefter, James
- Scheide, Lester
- Scherman, David
- Scherman, William
- Scherrer, G.C.
- Scherschel, Frank
- Scherschel, Joe
- Schickel, Richard
- Schiller, Lawrence
- Schlamm, William S. (Box Bio108-Bio109)